amw.com 2008-12-19

# FOX Broadcasting Company: Community

FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY PRIVACY POLICY

Effective as of May 1 2008

FOX Broadcasting Company ("FBC") is part of the News America Group, which has adopted a set of [Privacy Principles](http://www.newscorp.com/privacy.html)a> applicable to all its U.S.-based companies. FBC has implemented those Principles in this Privacy Policy, which describes how we collect, use and share personally identifiable information ("PII"-- that is, information such as your full name, email address, mailing address or telephone number) we obtain from and about individuals located in the U.S. both online and off-line.

Fox.com is a general audience web site and FBC does not knowingly collect PII from children under 13 years of age.

From time to time FBC may revise this Privacy Policy to reflect industry initiatives or changes in the law, our PII collection and use practices, the features of our web sites, or technology. If we make revisions that change the way we collect or use your PII, those changes will be posted in this Privacy Policy and the effective date will be noted at the beginning of this Policy. Therefore, you should review it periodically so that you are up to date on our most current policies and practices. If FBC materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your PII, your PII will continue to be governed by the Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change.

**COLLECTION:** COLLECTION OF PII BY FBC

General. FBC collects "PII" in order to create or enhance our relationship with you. When we collect PII from you it is because you are voluntarily submitting the information to us in order to participate in activities like sweepstakes, contests, games, surveys, forums, subscription registrations, in connection with content or suggestions you submit to us, chats or bulletin boards, or because you want us to furnish you with products, services or information. Fox.com message boards are operated by a third party vendor who collects PII, on FBCâ€™s behalf, submitted in the registration process. We may also obtain PII from reputable third parties.

Cookies. Cookies are small bits of information that the FBC web sites place on the hard drive of your computer. FBC uses cookies to identify your Internet browser and to determine whether you have installed the enabling software needed to access certain material on our web site(s). However, FBC does not use cookies or similar tools to collect or otherwise record any type of PII provided by or about any FBC web site visitor. The third party vendor who operates the fox.com message boards may set cookies on your computer in order to facilitate your use of this feature of our sites, such as storing your password for future visits.

Third party advertisements displayed on FBC sites may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers. FBC does not control these cookies and visitors to our web site(s) should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies. See the "Notice" section below for more information on third party advertisements.

FBC may use cookies and similar tools to relate your use of our web site(s) to PII obtained from you or a reputable third party. For example, if you've asked us to send you information about our upcoming products or promotions, cookie and/or click stream data about your activities on FBC web site(s) may allow us to limit the materials we provide you to items we think you will find interesting, based on your prior online activities and preferences. However, if FBC wishes to coordinate your personal and web site activity information in this manner, we will obtain your express affirmative consent. Information about your activities on FBC sites and other non-PII about you may also be used to limit the online ads you encounter to those we believe are consistent with your interests.

You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or to refuse cookies completely. However, without cookies you may not have access to certain features on FBC's web site(s).

**NOTICE:** FBC WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH NOTICE ABOUT ITS PII COLLECTION PRACTICES

When you voluntarily provide PII to FBC, we will make sure you are informed about who is collecting the information, how and why the information is being collected and the types of uses FBC will make of the information.

At the time you provide your PII, FBC will notify you of your options regarding our use of your PII (See "Choice" below). This Policy describes the types of other companies that may want to send you information about their products and services and therefore may want to share your personal information, provided you have given FBC permission to do so (See "Use" below).

Sometimes we collect PII from consumers in manual format or off-line, such as a post card or subscription form. Providing detailed notice in those situations often proves impractical, so consumers will instead be provided with a short notice that describes how to obtain the full text of this Policy and other relevant information from us.

FBC's web site(s) may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies. Some of these third party sites may be co-branded with an FBC logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by FBC. FBC's web site(s) also carry advertisements from other companies. FBC is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site(s) or for the privacy practices of third party or national Internet advertising companies. Once you've left an FBC site via such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party or advertiser site to determine how they will handle any PII they collect from you

FBC's web site(s) may also be linked to sites operated by companies affiliated with FBC (i.e., that are part of the News America Group). Although all News America Group entities adhere to the groupâ€™s [Privacy Principles](http://www.newscorp.com/privacy.html), visitors to those affiliated sites should still refer to their separate privacy policies and practices, which may differ in some respects from this Policy.

Some of the advertisements that appear on the FBC web site(s) are delivered to you by national Internet advertising companies such as DoubleClick. This company utilizes certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to the FBC web site(s), including information about the ads they display, via a cookie placed on your computer that reads (or approximates) your IP address. To opt out of information collection by these companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please visit: <http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy> or <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>.

**CHOICE:** FBC WILL PROVIDE YOU WITH CHOICES ABOUT THE USE OF YOUR PII

FBC will not use the PII you provide to us for purposes different from the purpose for which it was submitted, or share your PII with third parties that are not affiliated with FBC, unless you have chosen to receive certain information and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your PII.

**USE:** FBC'S USE OF PII

FBC will use your PII provided under this Policy in a manner that is consistent with this Policy. If FBC obtains PII from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is governed by this Policy. FBC may use PII in anonymous form for research and marketing purposes.

FBC may share your PII with companies that are affiliated with us (i.e., part of the News America Group of companies). And, provided you have given us permission, FBC may also share your PII with advertisers and business partners that are not affiliated with FBC, but would like to send you information about their products and services, such as sponsors of promotions, sweepstakes or programs that appear on the FOX Television Network. However, you will always have the opportunity to decline the option to receive information from unaffiliated third parties (and thereby not permit this sharing of your PII) when PII is collected.

FBC employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to obtain access to your PII. FBC may share your PII with outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities (i.e., message board administration, sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses), but they may only use your PII to provide FBC with a specific service and not for any other purpose.

FBC may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows FBC to customize the advertising and marketing messages you receive on our web sites. Your non-PII and click stream data about your activities on our sites may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished. These companies will not share your information with any third party or use it for any other purpose. Anonymous click stream, number of page views calculated by web beacons, and demographic information may also be shared with FBCâ€™s advertisers and business partners.

There may be instances when FBC may disclose PII without providing you with a choice in order to protect the legal rights of FBC, other companies within the News America Group or their employees, agents and contractors; to protect the safety and security of visitors to our web sites; to protect against fraud or for risk management purposes; or to comply with the law or legal process. In addition, if FBC sells all or part of its business or makes a sale or transfer of assets or is otherwise involved in a merger or business transfer, FBC may transfer your PII to a third party as part of that transaction.

**SECURITY:** FBC PROTECTS THE SECURITY OF PII

FBC uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel and physical measures to safeguard PII in its possession against loss, theft and unauthorized use, disclosure or modification. In addition, FBC uses reasonable methods to make sure that PII is accurate, up-to-date and appropriately complete.

**ACCESS, REMEDIES AND COMPLIANCE:** HOW TO ACCESS, CORRECT OR CHANGE YOUR PREFERENCES REGARDING YOUR PII AND HOW TO CONTACT FBC ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS

Whenever possible, visitors to FBC web sites may review the PII we maintain about them in our records. We will take reasonable steps to correct any PII a visitor informs us is incorrect. If you are a registered user of FOX.com, you can view your PII and user preferences by clicking the link at the bottom of any promotional email that is sent to you by FOX.com or by sending an email or writing to the FBC Privacy Officer (see contact information below).

If you ask FBC to stop using your PII, FBC will honor to that request while retaining any record of your PII that is necessary to comply with applicable federal, state or local law.

If you would like to communicate to us about this Privacy Policy or FBC's collection and use of your PII, to review or correct your PII, or to stop all future communication from us, please contact FBC's Privacy Officer, Mr. Hardie Tankersley at:

|   
---|---  
  
Email: 

| 

Mail: 

| 

10201 West Pico Boulevard  
Bldg. 100, 3220  
Los Angeles, CA 90035   
  
Phone: 

| 

(310) 369-3716   
  
Fax: 

| 

(310) 969-3300  
  
Please note that participation in certain activities on our web sites(s) may be limited if PII is not submitted by the visitor.
